Guide to the Winterhouse Art and Design Collection of Volume 1 Number 1
Yale University Arts Library
- 2013 Addition, 1991-2004
  - ACME Novelty Library ("Jimmy Corrigan: The Smartest Kid on Earth;" First in a Series of Fancy Pocket-Sized Chapters ...). Volume 6, Issue 5. Seattle, WA: Fantagraphics Books, Spring 1995. pp. 32. (Box 8, Folder 299)
  - CIO Insight. Premiere Issue. Number 01. New York, NY: Ziff Davis Media, May 2001. pp. 104. (Box 8, Folder 300)
  - n+1. Number One. New York, NY: n+1 Research, Fall 2004. pp. 182. (Box 8, Folder 301)
  - Rubber Blanket. No. 1. Hoboken, NJ: Rubber Blanket Press, 1991. pp. 48. (Box 8, Folder 302)
  - SPIRALS'91. Book 1 (and Book 2). Providence, RI: Graphic Design Department, Rhode Island School of Design, 1991. pp. 23, [1]. (and pp. 67, [5].). (Box 8, Folder 303)
    Book 1 and Book 2 of SPIRALS are bound together in the same volume as a tête-bêche, i.e., an upside-down or reversible book.
  - University Business. Volume 1, Number 1. New York, NY: University Business, LLC, March/April 1998. pp. 71. (Box 8, Folder 304)